Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.thirt Mss.B.B61.inventory13
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (T-V)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory13
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents T
  - Taber, Edith G. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
  - Taché, J. DeL. (Box 87)
    - To Barbeau, C.M., 1922 Feb. 1; 1p
  - Tackenberg, K. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p
  - Taft (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 13
  - Taft, Helen M. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Taft, William H. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Butler, K.M., 1905 Apr. 26
  - Taggart, Joseph (Box 87)
    - To Cattell, J. McKeen, 1917 Feb. 23
  - Tagliavini, G. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 28; 2p
  - Takagi, Yoshitaka (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 19; 1p
  - Tambo, R. (Box 87)
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 8
  - Tamentmun, Frank (Box 87)
    - To Boas
    - See Pegram, G.B.(to Cabanellas), 1937 Feb. 11
  - Tamss, F. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
  - Tannenbaum, E. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 17; 1p
  - Tao, Prof. Heng-Chih (Box 87)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1936, 1p
  - Tass Agency (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 30
    - Found at end of Oct. 1941, 1941 Dec. 25
  - Tate, Henry W. (Box 87)
    - From Boas, 1906 March 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Sep. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 May 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1911 May 20; 3p
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 May 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 17; 5p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 21
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 3; 8p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 2
    - To Boas, 1912 June 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 May 6
  - Tatum, S. L. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 5; 1p
  - Taub, A. (Box 88)
    - See King, C., 1931 Sep. 26
  - Taub, B. G. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 18; 1p
  - Tausen, Adolph (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 19; 2p
  - Tausig, L. G. (Mrs. Karl) (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p
  - Taussig, Frank W. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 10; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Pound, R.), 1933 May 23
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 25; 2p
    - To Seligman, E. R., 1926 Mar. 17; 1p
  - Tavenner, E. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 7; 1p
  - Tax, S. (Box 88)
    - See Boas, F. (to Wright, E.H.O.), 1931 Mar. 16
  - Taylor, Anne C. (Box 88)
    - See Boas, F. (to Nelson, T. and Sons), 1929 Nov. 4
    - See Boas, F. (to Nelson, T. and Sons), 1929 Nov. 6
  - Taylor, Archer (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Sapir, E., 1931 May 28; 1p
  - Taylor, C. Fayette (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 3; 1p
  - Taylor, H. L. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Taylor, L. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 22
  - Taylor, Mabel H. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 1p
  - Taylor, M. L. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 15; 2p
  - Taylor, P. S. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Tchernowitz, C. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Nansen, F., 1926 June 25
    - To Nansen, F., 1926 July 23; 1p
  - Teachers Union of the City of NY (Box 88)
    - See Boas, F., 1941 Apr. 14
  - Tead, Ordway (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 5; 1p
    - Enc. N.Y. Board of Higher Education (to Special Comm.), 1941 Apr. 24; 1p
    - Enc. Resolutions passed by the Board of Higher Education, 1941 Apr. 21
  - Techno-Service Corporation (Box 88)
    Scope and Contents note
    See Frank, Karl George
  - Tee-Van, Helen Damrosch (Mrs. John) (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Teeuwen, S. W. J. (Box 88)
    - From Kent, R. G., 1929 Apr. 17
  - Tegner, V. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1895 Aug. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Teichman, D. A. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 17; 1p
      Enc. Teichman, D.A. (open letter)
    - Open letter, 1935 Jan.
    - Enc. with Teichman, D. A., 1935 Jan. 17
  - Teichman, Sabina (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 28; 1p
  - Teichman, Mrs. S. -- (cont'd) (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 14; 1p
  - Teigan, H. G. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 8; 1p
      - Teigan, H.T., 1938 June 10; 1p
  - Teineholtz (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 1
  - Teit, James A. (Box 88)
    Native American Images note
    Folders #5, 20, 21: Kwakiutl baskets
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 June 13
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr.28
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 26
    - From Boas, 1908 June 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1909 May 14
    - From Boas, 1909 May 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 1; 4p
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1910 May 3
    - From Boas, 1910 May 31
    - From Boas, 1910 June 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1911 May 16
    - From Boas, 1911 June 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 June 9
    - From Boas, 1911 June 17
    - From Boas, 1911 June 20
    - From Boas, 1911 June 30
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1913 May 10
    - From Boas, 1913 May 13
    - From Boas, 1913 May 15
    - From Boas, 1913 May 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 July 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1916 May 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9
    - From Boas, 1917 June 1
    - From Boas, 1917 June 8
    - From Boas, 1917 July 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 June 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 10; 5p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 July 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jam. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 17
    - To Boas, 1908 June 26
    - To Boas, 1908 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 July 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 17
    - To Boas, 1909 May 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1909 June 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1909 June 14; 8p
    - To Boas, 1909 June 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1909 July 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 May 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 18; 9p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1911 May 4
    - To Boas, 1911 May 22
    - To Boas, 1911 May 31
    - To Boas, 1911 June 10
    - To Boas, 1911 June 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 22
    - To Boas, 1911 July 4
    - To Boas, 1911 July 7
    - To Boas, 1911 July 17
    - To Boas, 1911 July 23
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 July 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 May 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 6
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 June 12
    - To Boas, 1916 July 3
    - To Boas, 1916 July 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 22
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 26; 6p
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 June 6; 8p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 27
    - To Boas, 1919 July 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec.
    - See Columbia Univ. Dept. of Anthropology, 1919 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 May. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 20; 1p
    - See Columbia Univ., 1921 May 31 thru Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 July 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 30
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1907 June 22; 1p
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1910 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1911 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1911 Feb. 16
    - From Hatt, G., 1917 Apr. 13
    - From Neilson, John, 1918 Apr. 10
    - From Sargent, H.E., 1912 Aug. 1
    - From Scholefield, E.P., 1907 Apr. 24
    - To Smith, 1912 Feb. 8
    - From Smith, Harlan I., 1907 Apr. 23
  - Teit, Leonie J. (Mrs. J.A.) (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1923 July 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 9; 3p
  - Telfer (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1906 June 11
  - Tellez, I. G. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1930 June 17; 1p
  - Tellez, M. C. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Tello, Dr. Julio C. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p
  - Teneromo, I. (Box 88)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1911, 4p
  - Tentative plan for anthropological section of the Chicago World's Fair (Box 88)
    See folder: Chicago World's Fair
    - Found at end of Dec. 1930, 5p
  - Teny, S. C. (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 7
  - Terman, L. M. (Box 88)
    - See Boas, F. (to Woodworth, R.S.), 1931 Sep. 2
  - Termer, Dr. Franz (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 19; 2p
  - Terra, H. de (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1929 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 23; 2p
  - Terrill, Mary C. (Box 88)
    - To Singer, 1907 Mar. 25
  - Terry, G. C. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 10
  - Terry, James (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1888 May 22; 1p
  - Terry, Robert J. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 15; 3p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 1p
    - Enc. Committee on the study of the American Negro. Report, 1929 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 4; 1p
  - Tesniowski (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 7
  - Tessman, Gunter (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 7; 3p
    - Enc. Index of his monograph "Die Bubi" and catalog of the collection., 1924 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Teubner (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Textile Machine Works, Reading, Pa. (Box 88)
    See Gramm, Hanns
  - Thadburn, Robert (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1885 Apr. 28; 2p
  - Thade, Henry (Box 88)
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 12; 3p
  - Thalbitzer, Dr. William (Box 88)
    Folder #9: Inuit
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 5; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 1; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 6; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Sep. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 3p
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 May 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 1
    - To Boas, 1908 June 30
    - To Boas, 1908 July 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 May 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15
    - To Boas, 1917 July 29
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 24
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 4
    - To Boas, 1923 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1925 July 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 28; 3p
  - Thalheimer, A. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sep. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 13; 2p
    - See Spero, S.D., 1936 Feb. 5
  - Tharaldson, C. E. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 27; 1p
  - Thayer, Russell (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 12; 1p
    - Enc: Call to American Congress for peace and democracy., 1938 Nov. 3; 1p
    - See Lindeman, E.O., 1936 June 26
  - The Theatre Mass (Box 88)
    - See Burroughs, Eric, 1934 July 10
  - Theis, Sophie Van S. (Box 88)
    - To Burks, B. S., 1937 July 28; 1p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Committee), 1938 Oct. 25
    - To Burks, Barbara, 1937 July 28; 1p
    - To Burks, B., 1938 July 28; 1p
    - Found under, 1939 July 28
    - Boas. Paper on modern population at end of July 1939 as Enc.
  - Thelemann, Georg (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
  - Thelma (Box 88)
    See Adamson, Thelma
  - Thesun (Box 88)